<script data-react-helmet="true" type="application/ld+json">{"@context":"https://schema.org","@type":"LocalBusiness","name":"Hotondo Homes","url":"https://hotondo.com.au/","brand":{"@type":"Brand","name":"Hotondo Homes","logo":"https://cdn.productreview.com.au/resize/brand-logo/fd8cc6ea-7c59-34b9-b4ac-cdc3eea3488b?width=96&height=96&dpr=2&v=2"},"image":"https://cdn.productreview.com.au/resize/listing-picture/58d18a48-b3fc-32f4-873d-05c943c197b3?width=1200&height=630&withoutEnlargement=true&v=2","aggregateRating":{"@type":"AggregateRating","bestRating":5,"worstRating":1,"ratingValue":4.8,"reviewCount":824},"review":[{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/4d0efe70-272a-5933-a2c3-d8a8794dad33","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-04-08T05:13:20Z","headline":"Home Sweet Home","reviewBody":"It was a smooth process from point of sale to handover. Staff were great to deal with and the quality and attention to detail on the build were outstanding. Everyone went the extra mile to make our first home exceptional and we are so happy with the outcome. From the get go, I loved the facade and floor plan options and the ability to mix and match and the final result suits our tastes and lifestyle to a tee.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"CLAC","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/65f4f022-841a-5d4d-ac46-2f7cc23c7dac"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/7ce79e62-c6d4-5068-a329-049924ccff74","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-04-07T05:38:43Z","headline":"The perfect Extension! From single to double story - Duplex style!","reviewBody":"Project well managed from start to finish. Excellent communication skills. Always willing to discuss ideas and changes when any issues arose. Great experience with trends when it came to product selection and styles, more than happy with recommendations and choices. Tradespersons were always respectful and prompt when carrying out works. The structural works were completed in great time given issues with rain, building material supply and cost - which was critical to us as we were living in the building during the build. Ultimately would highly recommend, they took our dream of adding a second floor addition and made it a reality! Thankyou!","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Gordana P.","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/cd5c9538-78e0-4e22-a973-2201c548a336"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/ed04ad6c-0203-5054-bf8d-7f6d65f1e827","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-29T11:20:21Z","headline":"Just what we wanted","reviewBody":"The team at Hotondo were so professional and friendly throughout the process, dealing with Council and navigating some of the more complex aspects of the build. They kept us well informed throughout the design, DA application and build. The final product was just what we were looking for - Thank you","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Steve and Cheryl","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/da092ab4-3426-5d9e-9d29-fa73f35f0905"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/37110b8a-8573-5756-b0f3-0bb30627819c","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-25T03:01:53Z","headline":"Amazing company. We love our new home!","reviewBody":"We have just moved into our newly built home by Hotondo and honestly couldn't be any happier with the outcome of the build. The team at Hotondo homes were welcoming and supportive and communicative throughout the whole process. This made the whole process a lot less stressful as we knew we were in very good hands. Our build was very well managed by the Hotondo team. They're a very welcoming group of people that were always happy to give us an update on our build, have a chat over the phone or to answer any questions we had. We would definitely recommend going through Hotondo if you're looking or even considering at building. You won't be disappointed.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Katie","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/dc57d504-5eb2-5830-8d87-d9189c5b21dc"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/5920570e-c67a-512d-a610-aaf1d40e45c2","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-22T09:20:34Z","headline":"5 star service and friendliness from Hotondo Homes Raymond Terrace","reviewBody":"From the beginning the team were very accommodating, approachable and easy to communicate with. This helped with the design of our home, we love the finish with the beautiful raked ceilings and large alfresco outdoor area. Our build progressed smoothly and we managed to avoid any delays whilst building during Covid lockdown last year. Since handover, any issue that has arisen has been dealt with quickly.  \nOur experience of building our own home - a stressful one - was made easier by their attitude and flexibility. Thank you to everyone at Hotondo Homes Raymond Terrace, particularly owners Lyndsay and Jon, for making this a possibility in a difficult working climate. We appreciate everyone on the team and their contribution to getting us into our beautiful home.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"The vans","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/03ef6fe2-4375-5cbb-9ddf-ef0013f5a505"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/7f1c0003-4724-5c06-a672-b2918e31087a","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-21T06:08:23Z","headline":"My dream home","reviewBody":"I chose to build with Hotondo Inverloch after extensive research and 3rd party referrals and I’m glad I did. I have a beautifully built home that I am proud to call my own.\nAs a first time for me to build a home, there seems a lot to organise and decisions to be made. Caroline made the colour, flooring and cosmetic choices easy and Trent oversaw a smooth build. Despite navigating Covid, the build wasn’t significantly impacted which shows how well organised and planned their process is.\nI didn’t want a cookie cutter design and although I chose one of their base plans, I made changes to room sizes and layout to suit my needs. Nothing was an issue and everything was happily accommodated. Caroline kept me well informed of progress and next steps so I was completely comfortable in what was happening.\nThe end result is a beautifully built, distinctive home that I have been able to put my own style and touches on.\nIf you want a quality build, easy to deal with and flexible team, I’d highly recommend Trent and Caroline to build your home.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Sparky","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/02db33f4-7868-3b99-aacf-55300a46d7ff"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/f4c5f8f9-82ba-590b-86fd-93baff1486aa","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-18T04:34:14Z","headline":"Absolutely brilliant from start to finish!","reviewBody":"A huge thankyou to all the team at Hotondo Horsham, Everone from Annissa, who was an amazing help to find the perfect plan and home. And all the fantastic work from the admin team, Guy and Simon who kept me updated and were amazing throughout the whole build and made the entire process smooth from start to finish. All were incredibly accommodating to any plan changes and ideas I had, and all went above and beyond to ensure the end result was perfect!\nI couldn't be happier with the team at Hotondo Horsham - I highly recommend to anyone looking to build in Horsham.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Daniel","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/500f6127-ec8f-5aae-b6ef-15f93d2724e4"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/4f2c996c-87fd-5295-9cf8-31e1c724ba85","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-18T02:25:32Z","headline":"First Build & First Home","reviewBody":"As inexperienced first homeowners and first home builders, my partner and I were very appreciative of the help the Hotondo team was able to provide us.  Anthony, Lynelle, Ruth, and the whole team were very supportive, knowledgable, and pleasant to work with. Anthony was very accomodating and informative when it came to the specificities we were after in our design, Lynelle was amazing with colour selection, fixtures and fittings, and Ruth was always sure to gain answers to questions promptly. The team are fantastic and we will be forever grateful; the quality, workmanship, and attention to detail have impressed ourselves and our families so much that they have now chosen to build and work with Hotondo Homes Mackay. Although COVID restrictions and impacts were seen throughout Australia during our build, we never felt lost or uninformed throughout the process. From moving our sprinklers for us, coming over to help with questions, to installing our hoses for us, their kindness and assistance post-build are above and beyond! We will definitely be building with them again and would be delighted to refer anyone to work with them.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Ilona H","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/7daddf98-2a62-54a1-b820-ed10bab020a4"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/feca5442-7731-5ffc-9b33-6ad126674211","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-17T08:23:02Z","headline":"Great Home! Great Builder! Great Experience!","reviewBody":"We have just moved into our new home that Trent, Caroline and their team built for us. We'd never considered building until friends had Hotondo Inverloch build their townhouse and told us of their seamless experience with their build.\nCombined with the knowledge of Trent's high quality control of the build throughout was reassuring and Caroline's design expertise, we are delighted with our home.\nWe would be more than happy to recommend Hotondo Inverloch to anyone wanting to build.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Di and Steve","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/7ba7dd52-c210-5cfe-9881-7372e96edd70"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/aadad982-9851-5c69-8f47-47ee8cddba14","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-17T08:19:46Z","headline":"Highly recommended","reviewBody":"I highly recommend Hotondo Homes to anyone looking for a quality builder and an inclusive building experience as they manage most facets of the build 'in house' from subdivisions to planning etc.   \n\nFrom the competitive, transparent pricing to prompt and friendly customer service from Grace and the administration team, the building of our duplexes at Currarong have been seamless.  And the professionalism of how Adam operates his business and team, achieving the entire build on time and within budget was impressive. \n\nWe are very happy with the end result.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Brett Beverley","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/21561ba2-02b9-52a4-9fef-be49b8dbd492"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/cb0c9b45-88e5-59be-b3e3-4ec91d9b7f13","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-17T05:33:34Z","headline":"Perfect solution to our needs. fantastic progress","reviewBody":"From start to finish, what a great team form Grace and Kayla and the build team James, Mick and Adam, there were a couple of changes we wanted and nothing was a problem. They get it done and the price I was happy with. They designed the house to suit our block and its coming along better than expected.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Stephen","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/f21f5c45-8db6-3c54-b725-36aceef4957f"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/204c9567-675f-5879-9c3b-60eacdb14535","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-17T03:08:04Z","headline":"Very excited to get building with Hotondo","reviewBody":"My experience with Hotondo so far has been excellent and I would highly recommend the team. We designed a custom build, currently waiting council approval, and nothing has been a problem. The team have always been friendly, patient and accommodating, which has made, what is a stressful process, so much better. Henry is highly professional and a real asset to the company. A pleasure to work with.\nI can’t wait for the build to start and get into the beautiful home.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Nellie","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/be5f0685-7f26-3003-817a-a52a1dd618b7"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/19a650f7-3284-5952-a180-cb23333b0726","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-07T03:50:26Z","headline":"Our Forever Home is everything we Imagined!","reviewBody":"As this was the first time that we had ever built, we were nervous about who we chose to go through the experience with. From the moment we met Geoff S from Hotondo Jimboomba, we knew that we had found the right people to trust our dream with. \nWe had a very rough custom floor plan of what we wanted to include in our home, and Geoff and the team were able to bring it to life in a way that we hadn't even thought possible. \n\nWe had initially signed with another well known builder, but because our block didn't fit their cookie cutter mould, we ended up walking away, due to continually escalating costs that kept being added to their pricing. We always knew exactly where we stood with Hotondo. All of the fittings and finishings choices have been high quality.\n\nWe're so thrilled with our finished product and wouldn't hesitate to recommend the Three Geoff's (Geoff S, Geoff A & Geoff B), Donna, Erin, Zoe, Michael and the whole team.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Yvette B","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/e427c693-e20f-5891-850c-8f5b206e2527"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/819ed704-6f90-537b-a4d5-daf50602b655","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-03-04T15:51:02Z","headline":"Loving our new Erskine 225","reviewBody":"A bit shout out to the team at Hotondo Homes Launceston. They were very professional and dealt with our changes throughout the build with no fuss. The quality of there workmanship was first class and the finished product perfect in every way, on time and on budget, fantastic.\nWe intend building our forever home in 12 months time and given our true satisfaction with this build, we will not consider any one other than Sam and his wonderful team for our next project.\nThank you all so very much.......","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Darryl and Maree","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/a5467596-dfec-5612-86af-446e3e8a3e1d"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/6da0ce55-e370-5717-a3b8-76659af7eb02","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-28T07:11:28Z","headline":"Great experience so far!","reviewBody":"As an older investor, I looked at the challenges today of looking towards retirement. Bricks and mortar have always been a safe bet so when I decided to look at building an investment property I searched through some of my building choices.\nTo walk through the door into the Hotondo experience has been rewarding in itself, the staff at Hotondo South Coast are a credit to their business owners Adam and Sarah and also to the construction industry itself, we've all heard the negative stories, well not here. The moment you are greeted at reception by the delightful Grace and knowledgeable Kayla, the attention is on you and your new investment decision.\nHotondo Homes have such great building designs, pricing and house & land packages. Alex at Hotondo South Coast was able to walk me through some great choices that suited my budget.\nThe design team and consultants are all so welcoming to deal with, even choosing colours and where lighting should be (something I wouldn't have thought of) with Rachel was really hassle free. Adam's professional nature and knowledge of the building industry is astounding. Any questions or variations I requested at this stage he was able to address and solve with complete confidence and explaining so well that I could understand the processes from applications through to the future build.\nSigning up with Hotondo Homes has been a great decision. Dealing with the team at Hotondo South Coast has been a great experience. \nI know my future is in great hands!","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Ken N.","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/17af5d6b-e648-4f2b-a9ab-2bf53bd1ea3a"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/e8bf500a-0b8f-55a0-bb87-35c70eae8a00","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-28T00:39:06Z","headline":"Holiday House Build","reviewBody":"When the old holiday house was finally well past its used by date, we were keen to find a local builder who could work with us to adapt a design to suit our needs. From the very get go, Caroline and Trent were clear and responsive as we made our way through the initial stages. When we decided to progress with Hotondo the great experience continued. Despite building right through the middle of COVID, including building industry supply issues, we were kept informed along the way and the project remained on track to get the keys before Xmas. In the end we got the keys on Dec 22 and have been trilled with our new home, so much so, we spend more time here now than we do in Melbourne. As first time builders, we couldn't be more pleased with the experience we had with Hotondo Inverloch and the final product. We would recommend building with Trent & Caroline any time.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Steve M.","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/8753a28a-a504-4bb6-95b9-14a606c50a6b"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/a21a2815-63da-56ac-89f9-f79774cdea3a","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-23T02:23:06Z","headline":"Very Happy with Hotondo Communication, Care and Quality","reviewBody":"At the beginning we had a sense that Hotondo MNC hadn’t much experience building outside of a housing estate. This mainly related to a couple of over sights with the application of State Environmental Planning (SEP) instrument that lead to the requirement for an acoustic survey being required. Albeit none of this created much of an issue as Hotondo MNC was willing to work with us to resolve and move forward.\n \nOverall the building process and stages where clearly communicated and adhered to. Building during a statewide lockdown was a challenge for Hotondo MNC regarding inspections but the pictures provided in lieu of physical inspections was very helpful.\n \nThe trades people really need to be commended for the finish on the house. Little thigs like the long run of cornice in the living area is perfectly straight. All the skirting and architraves mitres have been cut perfectly and not just filled before painting. The same is for all the other elements of the house. \n \nWith only two very minor warranty issues at the final inspection speaks volumes to the quality and care shown by Hotondo MNC in producing our forever home. \n \nJust need to finalise the OC and everything will be perfect.\n \nThanks","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Mandy and Ian","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/5a7c18d1-f825-5457-ba42-3dc4a2dfe18c"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/991358d7-aa2e-50db-bc31-76057dd387db","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-22T18:11:31Z","headline":"Hotondo built our Dream Home","reviewBody":"Building my first home, it was Hotondo Ocean Grove I chose due to the respect and enthusiasm I got from the Home Sales consultant Richard compared to other builders when visiting the display center. He was extremely helpful in assisting me with what I could build within my budget, he made the process as seamless as possible and even assisted me with securing my block of land. Richard went above and beyond to bring ease to building my first home. The site supervisors were great to deal with, they always rectified any issues that came up and agreed to walk throughs at the different stages of the build. The cost estimate compared to the final costs were the same, and there were clear timelines set out at the start as to when to expect payments to be due. There was constant communication with the team at Hotondo throughout the build, and I felt very informed on the progress of the build. Hotondo Ocean Grove use local trades which is always great to see in a regional community. The design of the home feels unique, and the finishes on the house are high quality. Hotondo Ocean Grove built our dream home and I always recommend them to friends when they are looking for a builder in the area. Quality build and a great experience with the team, thanks so much Hotondo OG.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Karly M","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/1e2ec7ad-9199-5487-afae-b3f286bd91ce"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/72d90a81-0840-56ec-9fe4-98521ccc0ee2","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-22T17:45:38Z","headline":"Great builders, fantastic people and quality job","reviewBody":"What I loved about my build with Hotondo homes Wallan was the excellent communication that I received from the team. Even with several supply challenges, the team regularly communicated with me on the progress or what they were doing to resolve the problems with estimated project updates. \nOverall the level of trades was excellent, with the builders having a fine eye to details.\nKalen's patience and understanding what was important to us as clients ensured that the trades going on site knew clearly what to do and not to do.\nBeing a farm site all my fences/gates were respected and no stock were lost during the build reducing my stress levels. \nIf I was to do another build one day, I would certainly reach out to them.\nI highly recommend them on my experience.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Mal","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/04a2e80b-727e-5a7e-a9f0-397f06abd612"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/ae1e975b-62c9-5e6b-a420-e1070c49be5e","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-19T01:38:20Z","headline":"Service with ease","reviewBody":"The team at Hotondo Homes, Griffith NSW were great to build our first home with. \n\nA big thank you to Matt (Director) & Robert (Sales). They were able to provide all the right answers and solutions for any inquiries we had. \n\nIf we ever decide to build another home in the future, it will be a Hotondo Home. \n\nThanks Team!","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Jaeden Z.","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/ce82bd82-b1f2-4242-ad40-7bef54f5de09"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/62290ab7-aed1-53cd-bc3b-f0866e817bbf","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-18T06:27:41Z","headline":"Prompt after Service","reviewBody":"On completion of my 3 month maintenance list I received excellent customer service from Adam at Hotondo South Coast, who promptly arranged service providers. The 2 minor items I needed rectified were completed within one week of returned maintenance list, which was greatly appreciated. Highly recommended if considering Hotondo for your build!","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Lindsay E.","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/c2b300de-7d4f-4947-9b85-291b8e35211b"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/4a8673c1-7c70-5b06-9dd8-abf747d2092f","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-16T11:29:52Z","headline":"We highly recommend Hotondo Albury Wodonga","reviewBody":"Our first contact with Hotondo was met with understanding and helpfulness, the lady in the display home was amazing!\nThe owner of Hotondo came and immediately looked at the block, offering smart money saving alternatives to assist us in getting a view from the land.\nThe second Hotondo partner went the extra mile in helping the colour selection to be just right, driving me around various homes to visualize the finished product.  I was very grateful for her support and advice.\nThe supervisor was so experienced!  He made suggestions we hadn't thought of and gave us extra guidance in levelling out the outside of the block.  He was very accommodating to our needs.\nThe build was managed very well considering it was Covid times.  It took longer than it probably would have in a non Covid world. It was still finished in under the contract time frame.\nThe finished product is excellent and we are thrilled with the workmanship.\nOur final cost was more than the estimated cost because we were allowed to upgrade or make a few alterations to benefit us.  We made these alterations in full knowledge of the extra costs.\nWe highly recommend Hotondo Albury Wodonga to anyone who wants a quality build by a professional company who have experience and an attitude of helpfulness to make the build as stress free as it can be.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Ruth R.","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/7e33eeaf-d9ec-4535-bd17-25fcbc71a154"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/80841e19-7c6e-55be-83ae-e0fdc0443c37","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-15T23:04:33Z","headline":"Building Excellence","reviewBody":"This building team is truly excellent I cant speak more highly of there commitment to a great product result From the start of our Duplex project we had encountered like so many others Covid 19 which in it self led to material delays limited tradesman and who can forget all that heavy rain. But Adam Sturt from Hotondo Homes South Coast truly hangs on to the saying ,\"Its not the problem but how you fix it\" . He has a first class team behind him and wonderful management team led by Mick who also coordinated with precision our building supervisor James (thankyou James for answering all my annoying calls ) . This build looks amazing ,colour coordination by Rachael simply stunning.\nAnd thankyou so much to the office staff ,Kayla ,Grace, Stefanie and Sales consultant Alex ( you sell a great product keep it up ). Thanks again to you Adam for a job well done and thankyou to your lovely family for being there at our handover ,truly touching.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Ken Nicholls","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/b36b8393-f3d1-4568-b5e4-560f29a542a5"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/f9da8898-596c-556d-a4e3-4cab5d4c47a2","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-14T16:30:10Z","headline":"Beautifully built duplex","reviewBody":"Hotondo South Coast build our duplex in Shoalhaven Heads. From the start of the process, to the end the staff at Hotondo were very helpful - especially Jodie, Kayla, Luke, Mick, Stefanie and Adam. Build quality excellent, customer service equally good. The whole process was reasonably smooth, and even when there was a hiccup this was dealt with professionally and to our satisfaction. Would definitely use them again.","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Jennifer Percival","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/cc13ee4f-1c47-57fd-91b5-e9ed0c396ecc"}},{"@type":"Review","publisher":{"@type":"Organization","name":"ProductReview.com.au","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au"},"url":"https://www.productreview.com.au/reviews/7274f925-68fc-522c-ba97-cec45fd4d80e","inLanguage":"en-AU","datePublished":"2022-02-09T09:47:09Z","headline":"Our Dream Home by the sea at Inverloch","reviewBody":"We recently received the keys to our newly built home at Inverloch, built by Hotondo Homes Inverloch, and we are thrilled with the end result.  Thanks to Caroline, Trent and the team at Hotondo Homes Inverloch, our experience with the build was stress free and organised.  The quality detail and finish was of a high standard.  We are so pleased that we appointed a local Builder to build our dream home.  Thanks again to Caroline for her patience, guidance and advice on colour choices and selections, and would highly recommend Hotondo Inverloch.\nAlvano & Maria","reviewRating":{"@type":"Rating","ratingValue":5},"author":{"@type":"Person","name":"Alvano and Maria","sameAs":"https://www.productreview.com.au/consumer-profiles/b0de975c-9933-5df6-b604-2b951de76601"}}]}</script>
